<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Aamchi Mumbai</string>

    <string-array name="dashboardOptions">
        <item>About Us</item>
        <item>Contact Us</item>
        <item>Videos</item>
        <item>Gallery</item>
        <item>Visit Places</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="beaches">
        <item>Aksa Beach</item>
        <item>Kashid Beach</item>
        <item>Alibag Beach</item>
        <item>Gorai Beach</item>
        <item>Juhu Choupatty Beach</item>
        <item>Nagaon Beach</item>
        <item>Arnala Beach</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="waterParks">
        <item>Water Kingdom</item>
        <item>Suraj Water Park</item>
        <item>Tikujini Wadi Water Park</item>
        <item>Aqua Imagica</item>
        <item>Great Escape Water Park</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="temples">
        <item>Shree Sidhivinayak Temple</item>
        <item>Mahalaxmi Temple</item>
        <item>Babulnath Temple</item>
        <item>Tungareshwar Temple</item>
        <item>Walkeshwar Temple</item>
        <item>Mumba Devi Temple</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="malls">
        <item>RCity Mall</item>
        <item>Raghuleela Mall</item>
        <item>Infiniti Mall</item>
        <item>Oberoi Mall</item>
        <item>High Street Phoenix Mall</item>
        <item>Viviana Mall</item>
        <item>Palladium Mall</item>
        <item>Prime Mall</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="bestArchetecture">
        <item>Gateway of India</item>
        <item>Chatrapati Shivaji Maharaj Terminus</item>
        <item>Maharashtra Police Headquarters</item>
        <item>Taj Mahal Palace</item>
        <item>Chatrapati Shivaji Maharaj Vastu Sangrahalaya</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="markets">
        <item>Zaveri Bazar</item>
        <item>Chor Bazar</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="places">
        <item>Siddhivinayak Temple</item>
        <item>Gateway of India</item>
        <item>Hajiali</item>
        <item>Kanheri Caves</item>
        <item>Mount Merry Church</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_fullscreen">FullscreenActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

    <string name="aksaInfo"> \t \t \t Aksa Beach is a popular beach and a vacation spot in Aksa
        village at Malad, Mumbai, India. It is situated close to Malvani. It is a popular weekend
        destination . It is dotted with many private cottages and hotels, some of which are rented
        out to tourists and visitors. Aksa beach also happens to be one of the cleanest beaches in
        the city.\n \t \t \t It is accessible from Malad (West) station by select BEST buses from Borivali
        railway station, en route to Madh Island, and also by private transport and auto rickshaws.
        The beach is approximately 9 km from Malad station and 12 km from Borivali.\n \t \t \t It can also be
        reached from Andheri (West) railway station. It is not safe to swim as the currents are
        strong and the sands of the beach keep shifting because of the waves and people often
        misjudge them. It is not safe to swim as the currents are strong and the sands of the beach
        keep shifting because of the waves and people often misjudge them.</string>
    <string name="aksaAdd"> Aksa Beach, Malad West, Mumbai - 400095</string>
    <string name="kashidInfo"> \t \t \t Kashid is a complete getaway in every sense but the key reason for its immense popularity is that sits right between Mumbai and Pune. Proximity to two metros makes it a popular beach getaway near Mumbai and is quite crowded during weekends. If you are planning a trip here, it is suggested that you make reservations beforehand and save any last minute hassles.Kashid is the place for privacy as well as adventure. There are quiet spots for couples, ample space to pitch your tent and stargaze by the campfire, and a number of watersports to pump up your adrenaline.\n \t \t \t  The best time to visit Kashid Beach is between the winter season, i.e. between the months of October and February.\n \t \t \t  At Kashid Beach, weather is perfect during this time for enjoying all the beach strolling and water activities. There is no dearth of fun Kashid beach activities. It is a fun place to visit with your partner, family, or friends. Apart from water activities, which are totally spoiling, most fun things to do here are actually free of cost.</string>
    <string name="kashidAdd"> Kashid Beach, Maharashtra, India</string>
    <string name="alibagInfo"> \t \t \t Alibaug or Alibag is a coastal town and a municipal council in Raigad district of Maharashtra. Alibaug is surrounded by sea on three sides, it is very commonly known as the \'Goa\' of Maharashtra. The town was founded in the 17th century by Kanhoji Angre who was the naval chief during the reign of Shivaji Maharaj.\n \t \t \t  There are many options for tourists to reach Alibaug. Mumbai Airport is the nearest airport which is about 101 km from Alibaug. Pen Railway Station is the nearest railhead which is located at a distance of 28 km from Alibaug.Alibaug is well connected by bus with Mumbai, Lonavala, Pune, Ratnagiri and Kolhapur. Alibaug can also be reached by ferry from the Gateway of India in Mumbai. \n \t \t \t Homestays, resorts and hotels are available in Alibaug to suit every budget. Local residents also offer rooms in their houses for visitors to stay.The best time to visit Alibag beach is from October to March while November to February is the peak season.</string>
    <string name="alibagAdd"> Beach Road, Alibag, Maharashtra, India</string>
    <string name="goraiAdd"> Gorai, Mumbai, Maharashtra, India</string>
    <string name="goraiInfo"> \t \t \t Located in the north suburb of Mumbai, 40 kms from the main city, Gorai Beach is one the cleanest, most tranquil and one of the most frequented beaches of Mumbai. Located near Bhayandar, on the Gorai Creek, the soothing calmness of this beach bordering the Arabian Sea, makes for a perfect leisure weekend vacation. \n \t \t \t Other than the umpteen food shacks and street food options available at the spot, the beach is also replete with resorts and beach houses. Other than the numerous water sports, camel rides, boat rides and fun picnics, you can also rent one of these cottages to have a quiet private time with your friends and family. Dotted with beautiful palm trees and an all-around clean environment, the place is a hot favourite among tourists who want to spend a day away from the chaos and din of the city.\n \t \t \t  Since the beach is located on the outskirts of the city and boasts of surreal serenity, it is best picked among young couples who are looking for some solitude in the lap of nature. Besides, the presence of tourists, beach shacks and stay-in cottages makes for amazing full moon parties at the beach which draws tourist from far and wide.</string>
    <string name="juhuAdd"> Juhu, Mumbai, Maharashtra, India</string>
    <string name="juhuInfo"> \t \t \t The Juhu Beach in Mumbai is one of the most famous Indian beaches. This beach is known to be the one of the most-visited beaches of India and is situated in \'Ville Parle\'. It is located approximately 18 km from the city center and is a desired location for most film shootings. Juhu Beach borders a posh locality where most celebrities stay and therefore, it is quite common to find famous celebrities jogging along the sands of this popular beach of Mumbai.\n \t \t \t  The best time to visit Juhu Beach is from the months of October to February. It is best to avoid visiting the beach during the monsoon season as high tides are expected during this time. One of Mumbai\'s popular beaches and arguably the most-visited one, Juhu Beach is a perfect place to enjoy a lovely sunset. \n \t \t \t This beautiful beach, amidst the posh town of Mumbai, is a favourite hot-spot for many tourists. Most sightseers, who come here, enjoy the local delicacies sold at the many beach food stalls.</string>
    <string name="nagaonAdd"> Nagaon, Maharashtra, India</string>
    <string name="nagaonInfo"> \t \t \t Nagaon Beach is a beautiful beach situated 7 km from Alibaug on Alibaug-Revdanda route in the Raigad District of Maharashtra. The beach is surrounded by suru trees and cypress grove and is visited by number of tourists for its clean water. Water sports like boat ride, kayaking and island trips can also be enjoyed by the tourists. \n \t \t \t  This site is popular for picnic and weekend getaway, as there are numerous cottages, holiday homes, farmhouses and bungalows. Moreover, the beach is also famous among Indian film makers. \n \t \t \t Arabian Sea tides can be enjoyed by tourists along with betel nuts and coconuts available in abundance along the shores.</string>
    <string name="arnalaAdd"> Arnala, Virar West, Virar, Maharashtra - 401302, India</string>
    <string name="arnalaInfo"> \t \t \t The major attraction associated with Arnala is of course the Arnala Beach. The Arnala Beach happens to be centrally located and thus you can reach there by just walking down a few quick steps. From the beach, the Arnala fort island is visible at a distance, which was built originally by the Portuguese and then rebuilt by the Marathas. However, you need to get a ferry to reach the fort.\n \t \t \t  The tiny town of Arnala lies just seven kilometres west from Virar. For Mumbaikars, reaching Arnala would take not more than one and a half hours time. You can either take a bus or a private vehicle to reach Arnala directly. Another alternative is to simply hop onto the lifeline of Mumbai – the local trains and get down at Virar and reach Arnala by taking a rickshaw.\n \t \t \t sThis destination is known to be of national significance. The serenity of the place filled my mind with peace and calm. I would definitely recommend Arnala for Mumbaikars, who are seek an exciting weekend getaway.</string>


    <string name="sidTempAdd"> Siddhivinayak Mandir, Prabhadevi, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="sidTempInfo"> \t \t \t The Siddhivinayak Mandir evolved from a small, tiny place of worship to the Grand Temple that stands today in the later half of the twentieth century. Siddhivinayak is well known as "Navsacha Ganapati" or "Navasala Pavanara Ganapati" among devotees.The building was funded by a rich Agri woman named Deubai Patil. \n \t \t \t  Childless due to infertility, Deaubai built the temple so that Ganesha should grant children to other infertile women. Ramakrishna Jambhekar Maharaj, a disciple of the Hindu saint Akkalkot Swami Samarth, buried two divine idols in the front of the presiding deity of the temple on the orders on his guru. \n \t \t \t  It is claimed that after 21 years after the burial of the icons, a mandar tree grew at that spot with a svayambhu Ganesha in its branches, as prophesied by Swami Samarth.The Siddhivinayak temple receives donations of around ₹100 million (US$1.4 million) to ₹150 million (US$2.2 million) every year, which makes it Mumbai city richest temple trust. In 2004, the Siddhivinayak Ganpati Temple Trust, which operates the temple, was accused of mismanaging donations.</string>
    <string name="mahalaxmiTempAdd"> Mahalakshmi Mandir,Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="mahalaxmiTempInfo"> \t \t \t Built around 1785, the history of this temple is supposedly connected with the building of the Hornby Vellard. Apparently after portions of the sea wall of the Vellard collapsed twice, the chief engineer, a Pathare Prabhu, named Ramji Shivji Prabhu, dreamt of a devi statue in the sea near Worli. \n \t \t \t  The Mahalaxmi temple contains images of the Tridevi goddesses Mahakali, Mahalakshmi, and Mahasaraswati. All three images are adorned with nose rings, gold bangles and pearl necklaces. The image of Mahalakshmi is in the center shown holding lotus flowers in tandem. The compound of this temple contains several stalls that sell flower garlands and other paraphernalia used by devotees for worship and as offering. \n \t \t \t  During Navaratri celebrations, devotees from distant places throng to the temple, which is decorated for this occasion, to pay obeisance. They have to stand for hours in long queues holding coconuts, flowers and sweets which they offer to the goddess.</string>
    <string name="babulnathTempAdd"> Babulnath, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="babulnathTempInfo"> \t \t \t Babulnath Temple Shiva Linga and Idols were originally consecrated in the 12th century by the then Hindu king Bhimdev of the region. Over a period of time the temple was buried and lost over a period of time. When the first temple was built the land belonged to the Parsi community. \n \t \t \t  There were 5 Dakhma (Parsi final resting place) existing in the vicinity. There was a lot of resistance for the Parsi community at that time for building of the temple. This resistance continued till the late 1800 when the issue was settled by the courts in favour of the temple.The Babulnath Temple was patronised when built for the first time by Hindu merchant of that time and mainly the Gujarati community. \n \t \t \t  A bigger temple was built in 1890 by contributions from the Gujarati merchants and the likes of Maharaja Sayajirao Gaikwad of Baroda state. The current temple structure can be dated back to 1890.Currently the temple is thronged by people on Mondays and during Mahashivratri, Shravan months.</string>
    <string name="tungaTempAdd"> Tungareshwar Temple,sativli, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="tungaTempInfo"> \t \t \t Surrounded by lush greenery, waterfalls and thickets of forests, the Tungareshwar Temple apart from being a religious site, is also a nature lover delight. The temple is located on the hilly slope of the Tungareshwar Hill.  \n \t \t \t  A river flows just below the temple and there a number of picturesque waterfalls in the vicinity. The temple is a bit of a climb, but the surrounding natural beauty makes the journey enjoyable.There are two smaller shrines built outside the main temple. A number of local deities along with Durga, Ganesha, Rama and Hanuman are also worshipped here.Local Govt and Temple authorities to seriously look into improve access to be proper and safe for all types of vehicles and pedestrians to attract more devotes and tourists.  \n \t \t \t Currently access is with raw and sharp boulders cover.</string>
    <string name="walkTempAdd"> Walkeshwar Temple, Malabar Hill, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="walkTempInfo"> \t \t \t Walkeshwar Temple, also known as the Baan Ganga Temple, is a temple dedicated to the Hindu god, Shiva located in Walkeshwar, near Malabar Hill neighbourhood, in South Mumbai precinct of the city of Mumbai, India. It is situated at the highest point of the city, and close to the temple lies the Banganga Tank. \n \t \t \t  The temple and the attached fresh water Banganga Tank were built in 1127 AD by Lakshman Prabhu, a Gaud Saraswat Brahmin minister in the court of Silhara dynasty Kings who ruled Thane, and the islands of Mumbai during 810 to 1240 AD. The temple was destroyed by the Portuguese during their reign over Mumbai in the 16th century.It is currently the site of an annual Hindustani classical music festival, which in 2005 featured musicians like classical singers Rajan and Sajan Mishra, and Santoor maestro Shivkumar Sharma. \n \t \t \t  Branches of Shri Kavle Math and Shri Kashi Math, famous religious seats of Gaud Saraswat Brahmins, are located on the northern and western banks of the tank, respectively.</string>
    <string name="mumbaTempAdd"> Mumba Devi Mandir, Bhuleshwar, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="mumbaTempInfo"> \t \t \t This temple was built in honour of the Goddess Amba. The Mumbadevi temple is six centuries old. The first Mumbadevi temple was situated at Bori Bunder, and is believed to have been destroyed between 1739 and 1770. \n \t \t \t  The original temple built at the site where the Victoria Terminus station earlier was by Koli fishermen was demolished around 1737 and a new temple was erected in its place at Phansi Talao.The present name of the city is derived from the Goddess Mumbadevi. The temple itself is not impressive but is an important landmark as it is dedicated to MumbaDevi, the city patron deity.The temple is dedicated to goddess parvati also known as gauri in her Fisher woman form. To take the form of mahakali, goddess parvati had to gain perseverance and concentration. The Mumbadevi road is to the right from the northern end of Zaveri Bazaar. \n \t \t \t  It is not uncommon for visitors of Mumbai to pay their respects at the temple and is one of the tourist destination.</string>


    <string name="waterkAdd"> Water Kingdom, Borivali, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="waterkInfo"> \t \t \t Water Kingdom is one of its best and biggest theme and water park located at Borivali coastal area (Gorai Creek) of Mumbai suburban area. Nearest railway station to reach Gorai is Borivali, Yet many also commute via Bhayandar station.  \n \t \t \t  This 64 acres huge park surrounded by nature and greenery is owned and managed by ‘Pan India Paryatan Pvt Ltd’ (PIPPL), The Essel World Group. Its a famous picnic spot and tourist attraction specially during summer. It has varieties of water rides for kids and adults both, with DJ and rain dance facility inside which attracts major youth. All safety and basic facilities like Shower, Dress changing, Drinking water, First aid, Counters for baggage are available in Water Kingdom at reasonable price. Water inside all pools is regularly maintained and taken care of hygiene, Also people with skin disease or allergy are restricted.  \n \t \t \t  Giant water rides like water splash slide and zig zag between woods are also available.</string>
    <string name="surajwpAdd"> Suraj Water Park, Dongripada, Thane West, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="surajwpInfo"> \t \t \t Suraj Water Park is also known as The Pride of Maharashtra after having bagged 6 Times winner in Limca Book of Records and winner of National and International awards.Created by Muchhala Magic Land Pvt. Ltd.  \n \t \t \t  Suraj Water Park is a rare combination of Modern Technology and traditionalist making it a kind of place for exhilarating thrills and funs. The statue of Lord Shiva with Ganga originating from his hair-lock as in Indian mythology is adorned by water-slides for children. At Suraj Water Park, the water rides are not just dumped but each has the importance of giving thrill and challenge. \n \t \t \t  A visit to the Suraj Water Park is the perfect way to spend the day, filled with fun and amusement. The wave pool, stimulating the waves of sea, is a big hit amongst the kids. Just opposite to it is the Crazy River, which imitates the speed and turbulence of an actual river. Near it lies the Lazy River, the perfect place to relax and let yourself float on the rubber floats, till it joins with the wave pool. The slides at the Suraj Water Park provide you with the adrenaline rush and are perfect for the fun-seekers. \n \t \t \t  You can enjoy the slide either on your own car or with your family, on a rubber float. </string>
    <string name="tikujiniwadiAdd"> Tikuji-Ni-Wadi, Thane, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="tikujiniwadiInfo"> \t \t \t Tikuji-Ni-Wadi is an amusement park, water park, and a resort near Mumbai and at Thane. |The amusement park includes go-karts, roller coasters, giant wheels and water park. Additionally, there is a Shiva temple and marriage halls as a part of the resort. During Shivaratri, they make Shiva replica out of ice.  \n \t \t \t  The park remains open during the rainy season. In 2013, a realistic-looking dinosaur park was started. The park, spread over 20 acres (8.1 ha) of land, is popular for greenery and a "UFO ride". Except the water and amusement parks, there are several other activities and attractions such as go-karting, bumper-boats, dinosaur world, 9D adventure, aquarium and farm.  \n \t \t \t  The place is situated in Thane so commuting to and fro is easy. The staff are also very polite and helpful.</string>
    <string name="aquaIwAdd"> Aqua Imagica, Khopoli, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="aquaIwInfo"> \t \t \t Aqua Imagica is a 130-acre theme park in Khopoli, India. It is owned by Adlabs Entertainment Ltd. \n \t \t \t  The park has an estimated daily capacity of 15,000 visitors. To date, the park has hosted over 3.5 million visitors.Zip Zap Zoom is a high-speed mat racer that sends riders through enclosed aqua tubes that run closely alongside each other.The vertical height of ride is 104 feet.It is listed in Limca Book of Records in 2014. Floatsa involves riders getting into big rubber tubes and floating in the pool of water, as a gentle current takes them downstream. It is an individual ride meant for the purpose of relaxation.A music and water attraction for the kids with five wild animals as characters. \n \t \t \t  The Zooballoo ride plays music and simultaneously splashes the children with water, as they dance along.Kiddie pool is a small pool for children to play in. It has a depth of about 3 feet.</string>
    <string name="greatewpAdd"> Great Escape Water Park, Virar, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="greatewpInfo"> \t \t \t A day picnic at Virar’s lush green area at Great Escape Water Park studded amongst the picturesque mountains of Pelhar, is best option with enjoying 16 rides, Unlimited tasty vegetarian food, DJ Rain dance and lots more.  \n \t \t \t  It is best to escape a day from the routine life... Great Escape is a Pure Veg Only Water park. Alcohol is not allowed or available inside. An Ideal water park for Jain Community people in Mumbai.  From virar (e), take st bus for vajreshwarior auto rickshaw to the great escape water park.nothing beats the feeling of traveling with your family and friends on a long drive. coming by car from mumbai, take western express highway (weh), drive down on nh8 (ahmedabad highway), enjoy the landscapes, take first right after virar phata, drive down to parolnaka and take a right and you are the fun destination.Please note that the tickets are issued only for the date as mentioned thereon. \n \t \t \t  These tickets cannot be used on any other date, no refunds shall be given for unused tickets.</string>


    <string name="zaveribAdd"> Zaveri Bazaar, Bhuleshwar, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="zaveribInfo"> \t \t \t Zaveri Bazaar is a jewelry market and a major hub for B2B and B2C jewelry industry in Mumbai, India. \n \t \t \t  Located at Bhuleshwar in South Mumbai, just north of Crawford Market, Zaveri Bazaar is a muddle of narrow lanes, dotted with hundreds of jewelry shops that sell gems and jewels, notably Tribhovandas Bhimji Zaveri (TBZ), Dwarkadas Chandumal, Dhirajlal Bhimji Zaveri and UTZ. 65% of all gold trading and dealing in India is estimated to originate from the market.Zaveri Bazaar is regarded as being secured because it has CCTVs installed in order to avoid almost any crime, private protection involved for every shop, the industry is under 24 hours vigilance because it does a huge trade in diamond and also other metal jewellery. Zaveri Bazaar is also famous for photo frames, clips, tea-sets, dinnerware, toys and other luxury lifestyle articles crafted out of expensive metals. \n \t \t \t  Zaveri Bazaar gets the maximum credit of jewellery and gems export from the country.It has been the target of three attacks in Mumbai since 1993. It was one of the 12 areas bombed during the 1993 Bombay bombings, followed by the 25 August 2003 Mumbai bombings and the more recent 13 July 2011 Mumbai bombings.</string>
    <string name="chorbAdd"> Chor Bazaar, Grant Road, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="chorbInfo"> \t \t \t Chor Bazaar is one of the largest flea markets in India, located near Bhendi Bazaar in Grant Road, South Mumbai. \n \t \t \t  The area is one of the tourist attractions of Mumbai. The word chor means thief in Marathi and Hindi. According to popular legend, if you lose anything in Mumbai you can buy it back from the "Chor Bazaar".In modern times, Chor Bazaar is said to sell mostly second-hand goods rather than stolen goods. \n \t \t \t  The market is now famous for antique and vintage items.A store called Mini Market offers old Bollywood posters for sale.The market has been mentioned in popular novels, including Rohinton Mistry Such a Long Journey, where it is described as "not a nice place". The Spool Man (2016) - A short documentary about a Chor Bazaar shop-keeper, directed by Daniel Ifans, produced by We Are Tilt. Official Selection at Ethnografilm Film festival 2019 (Paris, France).</string>


    <string name="gatewayAdd"> ThTee Gateway of India, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="gatewayInfo"> \t \t \t The Gateway of India is an arch-monument built in the early twentieth-century located in the city of Mumbai, in the Indian state of Maharashtra. \n \t \t \t  After its construction the gateway was used as a symbolic ceremonial entrance to British India for important colonial personnel. It has been called a symbol of "conquest and colonisation" commemorating British colonial legacy. The gateway is also the monument from where the last British troops left India in 1948, following Indian independence.The gateway was the site of a terror attack in August 2003, when there was a bomb blast in a taxi parked in front of it. Access to the gateway was restricted after people congregated at its premises following the 2008 Mumbai terror attacks, in which the Taj Hotel opposite the gateway and other locations in its vicinity were targeted.The gateway has interested companies and corporate houses such as the Tata Group, the RPG Group, and the JSW Group, who have expressed their wish to maintain the gateway and enhance its facilities. \n \t \t \t  This happened after the state government identified 371 heritage sites under its Maharashtra Vaibhav State Protected Monuments Adoption Scheme. The gateway is amongst the prime tourist attractions in Mumbai. The gateway is a protected monument in Maharashtra under the aegis of the Archaeological Survey of India (ASI). It is a regular gathering place for locals, street vendors, and photographers. In 2012, the Maharashtra Tourism Development Corporation moved the Elephanta Festival of Music.</string>
    <string name="csmtAdd"> Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj Terminus, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="csmtInfo"> \t \t \t Chhatrapati Shivaji Terminus (officially Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj Terminus) (station code: CSTM (mainline)/ST (suburban)), also known by its former name Victoria Terminus (station code: BBVT/VT), is a historic terminal train station and UNESCO World Heritage Site in Mumbai, Maharashtra, India. \n \t \t \t  The terminus was designed by British architectural engineer Frederick William Stevens in the style of Victorian Italianate Gothic Revival architecture.The railway station was built to replace the Bori Bunder railway station, in the Bori Bunder area of Bombay, a prominent port and warehouse area known for its imports and exports.The interior of the building was conceived as a series of large rooms with high ceilings. It is a utilitarian building and has had various changes required by the users, not always sympathetic. It has a C-shaped plan which is symmetrical on an east-west axis. All the sides of the building are given equal value in the design. It is crowned by a high central dome, which acts as the focal point.  \n \t \t \t  The dome is an octagonal ribbed structure with a colossal female figure symbolizing Progress, holding a torch pointing upwards in her right hand and a spoked wheel in her left hand.CST has a total of 18 platforms—seven platforms are for suburban EMU trains and eleven platforms (Platform 8 to Platform 18) are for long-distance trains.  \n \t \t \t  The station has been the location of filming the "Jai Ho" song in Slumdog Millionaire.</string>
    <string name="policehAdd"> Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj Marg, Colaba, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="policehInfo"> \t \t \t The Maharashtra Police Headquarters was shifted to the present heritage building in Year 1982. At that time, the state police force with a strength of 87000 was headed by an officer of the rank of Inspector General of Police. Today, the force has increased beyond 2,00,000 and is headed by the Director General of Police.  \n \t \t \t  The building is divided into two wings, the north one being 110 feet by 58 feet and the south wing was originally allocated as quarters for the superintendent. Dining rooms for officers and sailors were located to the north end of the ground floor with a grand entrance hall with a paneled teak ceiling at the centre. Iron railings placed on neatly designed ground arches protect the blue basalt stone stairs. The southern half of the ground floor accommodated a large library, the superintendent′s office and storerooms.The entire work was carried out under the supervision of J H E Hart, MICE from February to November 1872; Col J A Fuller, RE from November 1872 to February 1876 with F W Stevens as Executive Engineer in charge and Sitaram Khanderao Vaidya as Overseer. \n \t \t \t  The building houses the offices the offices of the Director-General of Police and is the nerve centre of the policy making, planning and implementation for the State Police. Shri K.P. Medhekar was the first incumbent in this building. Since then, this building has seen 24 DGs.</string>
    <string name="tajAdd"> The Taj Mahal Palace Hotel, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="tajInfo"> \t \t \t The Taj Mahal Palace Hotel, is a heritage, five star, luxury hotel built in the Saracenic Revival style in the Colaba region of Mumbai, Maharashtra, India, situated next to the Gateway of India. Historically it was known as the "Taj Mahal Hotel" or the "Taj Palace Hotel" or simply "the Taj". \n \t \t \t  Part of the Taj Hotels Resorts and Palaces, this hotel with its 560 rooms and 44 suites is considered the flagship property of the group, it employs some 1,600 staff. The hotel is made up of two different buildings. Taj Mahal Palace Hotel was specifically chosen by Lashkar-e-Taiba, a terror group who attacked multiple targets, for an attack so that it will be "striking a blow against a symbol of Indian wealth and progress". The hotel was attacked on 26 November 2008, during which material damage occurred, including the destruction of the hotel roof in the hours following. Hostages were taken during the attacks, and at least 167 people were killed, including many foreigners. \n \t \t \t  On 6 November 2010, U.S. President Barack Obama became the first foreign head of state to stay at the Taj Mahal Palace after the attacks. In a speech from the terrace of the hotel, Obama said that "the Taj has been the symbol of the strength and the resilience of the Indian people" .</string>
    <string name="vastuAdd"> The Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj Vastu Sangrahalaya, Fort, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="vastuInfo"> \t \t \t The Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj Vastu Sangrahalaya, abbreviated CSMVS and formerly named the Prince of Wales Museum of Western India, is the main museum in Mumbai, Maharashtra. It was founded in the early years of the 20th century by prominent citizens of Mumbai, with the help of the government, to commemorate the visit of George V, who was Prince of Wales at the time. \n \t \t \t  The Museum was established under Bombay Act No. III of 1909. The museum is now maintained by annual grants from the Government and the Bombay Municipal Corporation. The latter pays for these grants from the interest accruing on the funds at the disposal of the Trust of the Museum. The museum miniature collection encompasses representations of the main schools of Indian painting namely, Mughal, Rajasthani, Pahari and Deccani. It features palm leaf manuscripts dating to the 11th-12th centuries to the early 19th century pahari paintings, as well as paintings from the Sultanate period. \n \t \t \t  Notable manuscripts housed in the museum include the Anwar-Suhayli painted in Mughal emperor Akbar studio and a 17th-century manuscript of the Hindu epic Ramayana from Mewar.</string>


    <string name="rcityAdd"> R City Mall, Ghatkopar West, Mumbai, Maharashtra </string>
    <string name="rcityInfo"> \t \t \t R City Mall is a shopping mall located in Ghatkopar West, Mumbai. The mall spreads across 1.2 million square feet with the capacity to house over 350 stores. The mall has over 194 shopping stores, over 66 food outlets, 10 entertainment areas, 3 ATM facilities, 13 useful service areas, and a Movie Theatre (INOX Leisure Limited). \n \t \t \t   The mall was opened in two phases, the total size of the first phase of the development is 750 thousand square feet.R-City Shopping Mall is located at Ghatkopar and is huge. With so many shops, you have everything under one roof - from restaurants to gaming zones to favorite Max, BigBazaar, Spa, and what not. With more than 200 + stores, you are never ever off options. \n \t \t \t  With multiple options for kids to remain engaged, and with a open area, there is nothing more one can ask for. You name it you have it.. be it KFC, Dominos, McD, CCD, Fridays, Zaffran, Rajdhani. There is also a multplex from INOX that has 9 screens.</string>
    <string name="raghulelaAdd"> Raghuleela mall, Vashi, Navi Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="raghulelaInfo"> \t \t \t Raghuleela is a mall situated in Vashi, Navi Mumbai, India. Developed by Raghuleela Properties Pvt.Ltd., Raghuleela Mall is a 4-storeyed air-conditioned mall covering an area of approximately 375,000 sq ft (34,800 m2) on each floor with lifts, escalators and central staircase atrium to connect all the four levels. \n \t \t \t  The mall has daily footfall of upto 30,000 shoppers.This mall is located right next to Vashi station and is crowded most of the time. People come here to watch movies and do shopping.The Mall has lost its charm after Central shifted to its own exclusive building. A multiplex is now the only attraction other than Big Bazaar. \n \t \t \t  xIt is favourite hangout of college students with busy food stalls and budget shops with perpetual sales.</string>
    <string name="infinitiAdd"> Infiniti Mall, Malad, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="infinitiInfo"> \t \t \t Infiniti Mall is a chain of shopping malls in India. It is a subsidiary of K. Raheja Constructions, which has been in the business of construction and property development since the 1960s. The first Infiniti Mall opened in 2004, in Andheri, Mumbai. Infiniti Mall launched their second property in Mumbai, at Malad, in May 2011. \n \t \t \t  Infiniti Mall, Malad is located on New Link Road, Malad (West). It is one of the biggest malls in Mumbai. It was built in 2011 and is spread across 302,349 square feet (28,089.1 m2). The mall has shopping stores, a multiplex, food court and a play area. The mall has five floors excluding basements and consists of more than 180 brands. \n \t \t \t  There are 36 food outlets in the food court which comprises quick-service restaurants, kiosk and cafes and restaurants.</string>
    <string name="oberoiAdd"> Oberoi Mall, Goregaon, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="oberoiInfo"> \t \t \t Oberoi Mall is a one stop destination for Fun, Food, Fashion, and Films. Oberoi Mall has found a unique niche amongst quality conscious and discerning customers and offers facilities that include two levels of basement parking with capacity for approximately 1,000 cars, a large central atrium with natural light, elevators and escalators for internal circulation, central air-conditioning and an integrated building management system. \n \t \t \t  Oberoi Mall is located at just walkable distance from my house, have visited the mall many times with my hubby, parents. \n \t \t \t  Very clean and neat mall with lot of branded shops for Garments, Electronic Accessories etc.</string>
    <string name="phoenixAdd"> High Street Phoenix, Lower Parel, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="phoenixInfo"> \t \t \t High Street Phoenix, formerly known as Phoenix Mall, is one of the largest shopping malls in India, situated in Lower Parel, Mumbai. Its gross floor area is 3,300,000 square feet (310,000 m2).It is a luxurious mall in Parel, featuring luxury brands like Gucci, etc. In addition to the mall, the compound hosts a five-star hotel, a multiplex, commercial space and a residential tower. \n \t \t \t  The mall consists of the Palladium, SkyZone and Grand Galleria. South Asia largest 20 lane bowling concourse, was first started here in 1996. India first Hyper market concept Big Bazaar was introduced in 2001 at High Street Phoenix.In 2007, Phoenix Mills announced the development of Market Cities in Mumbai, Pune, Bangalore and Chennai. \n \t \t \t  In Bangalore they have developed the residential project named as One Bangalore West in the heart of the city, Rajajinagar which is also listed amongst the tallest building in Bangalore. In Pune they are developing a residential property named as Phoenix Fountainhead near by Phoenix Market City.</string>
    <string name="vivianaAdd"> Viviana Mall, Thane West, Thane, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="vivianaInfo"> \t \t \t Viviana Mall is the best Mall in Thane, which offers ample of shopping facilities with International and Indian brands, Huge Food court and well maintained seating capacity, kids play area and multiplexes offers an one stop locations of entertainment.It is a good place to do some sensible shopping. Most stores stock more than 5 brands, so you can compare styles, prices and quality before you make your purchase. \n \t \t \t  Put on comfortable shoes as there is a lot of walking to do. The information desk is always manned and they are quite helpful. There are prams that you can rent at the entrance, if you need. I found the rest rooms were placed very far apart and if one is being serviced, the walk to the next one can be quite a trek. \n \t \t \t  Also, air conditioning can be an issue in some stores.</string>
    <string name="palladiumAdd"> Palladium Mall, Lower Parel, Mumbai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="palladiumInfo"> \t \t \t Palladium is a nice place to spend time having major international brands and a huge area to host its visitors. You could enjoy your shopping spree here with most of the international designer brands found here. This includes clothing, perfumes, fashion, accessories etc. The eatery section is found outside the mall with many varieties to satisfy our cravings. \n \t \t \t  The young crowd enjoys more here since many options are found for their interests.Palladium Mall is located on Senapati Bapat Marg, in the Lower Parel district. In fact, this is not a mall, but a modern extension to the big, older High Street Phoenix Mall. Beautiful modern design. Very clean. \n \t \t \t  Firms of different price categories are represented. During weekends, there are a lot of people here.</string>
    <string name="primeAdd"> Prime mall, Vile Parle West, Mumbai</string>
    <string name="primeInfo"> \t \t \t prime mall, Mumbai is a perfect destination for a great time with your dear ones. Enjoy the attractions of this popular tourist spot. With so much to lure your senses and offer you recreation at its best, get drenched in the spirit of adventure that you get to explore at prime mall, Mumbai. Enjoy together all the points of popular interests and bring back several memorable moments. \n \t \t \t  prime mall, Mumbai is not just the place for sightseeing, but it also enables you to steal a self-indulgent moment for yourself as well. So, check out the prime mall tourist spot for all the attractions that is on offer and visit this spot on weekends for a rejuvenating time. World standards, extraordinary architecture, innovative layouts, and well-thought execution make place a highly coveted point of tourist interest. Do not forget to carry your camera and capture special moments. \n \t \t \t   prime mall, Mumbai is the sure way to refresh and relax after a busy weekday. Explore interesting themes, fabulous designs, colorful landscapes, amusing characters, ambient music, props and merchandise available in nearby stores- all at one place. prime mall, Mumbai is the best way to have a memorable time with kids and family. So, enjoy a fulfilling outing at prime mall in Mumbai.</string>

</resources>
